

FAITH T. DAAL

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

CONTACTS

faith.daal08@gmail.com

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

University of Cebu - Class of 2017

- Received a Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

INTRODUCTION

I am an experience front-end web developer for five years who is self-motivated and willing to learn new technologies. I am looking for a position to grow more on my career, skills, and passion while contributing for the success of company as well.

TECHNICAL SKILLS:

- AngularJS - ReactJS

- HTML/CSS - FS6

- Saga

- Redux - Material UI

- Javascript

- UI/UX

- CSS preprocessors like SASS and Stylus

- Rest API - Agile Methodology

- TailWind CSS - Vue.js

WORK HISTORY

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Agile Wave Technologies June 2021 - August 2022

- Responsible to convert the mockup designs
- Responsible to integrate data from the front-end to back-end side
- Responsible to QA before and after production
- Responsible to assist client needs

NO-CODE AND LOW-CODE DEVELOPER

Upwork

January 2021- June 2021

- Responsible to understand client's needs
- Responsible dealing database management
- Responsible deployment both Android and Apple

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Medspecialized Inc. May 2017 - January 2021

- Responsible to send, validate and receive data from user to backend thru Rest API
- Responsible for project management for a specific task
- Responsible to communicate well with my co-teammates for our task assigned
- Responsible for QA of the functions and UI/UX experience
- Database planning

LEAD GENERATION / VA

Your Virtual Sidekick Inc.

November 2020 - March 2021

- Responsible to answer all the messages on the LinkedIn
- Responsible to find possible leads, 25-30/day
- Responsible updated the excel sheets
- Responsible to communicate to my client for the updates

SOCIAL MEDIA CONTENT CREATOR / VA

Your Virtual Sidekick Inc. January 2020 - November 2020

- Social media management
- General Admin Tasks
- Research
- Data Entry